tapinto.net 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | TAPinto

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
for TAPinto.net

Last update:  February 27, 2019

TAPinto.net, hereinafter referred to as TAP ("TAP") is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our Web site (the "Site") as well as the privacy of registered users of the interactive features of the Site (“Users”). As part of our commitment to protecting your privacy online, we have written this policy to help you understand how we gather information about users of the Site, how we use the information we gather and what steps we take to protect the information you share with us.

For unregistered visitors, we've structured the Site so that, in general, you can visit us on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

If and when you choose to provide us with personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with TAP.

**What information do we collect and why?**

TAP reserves the following rights regarding the information you submit:

**Type of Information**

| 

**How and Why We Use It**  
  
---|---  
  
Your name, email address, phone number and other contact or payment information you submit

| 

  * To include you on our mailing list
  * To communicate with you
  * To respond to your specific requests
  * To process accounts and provide newsletters

Information about what pages you have viewed

| 

  * To improve our Site
  * To provide visitor assistance

Information about your location (based on Internet Protocol (“IP”) address) and your device (hardware type, hardware identifier, device name, operating system version, unique device ID (persistent / non-persistent), media access control (“MAC”) address, international mobile equipment identity (“IMEI”)

| 

  * To provide account support and troubleshooting
  * To calculate aggregated, anonymous statistics on visitors to the Site
  * To better operate our Site

Non-personally identifiable, aggregated, information regarding what pages of the Site you choose to access, traffic patterns, demographics, and other statistics about our site and our users

| 

  * For analytics, targeting, monitoring, marketing, demographic, and promotional purposes as well as to assist us in customizing the content of our Site
  * To produce statistical and/or demographic data for use by advertisers, potential advertisers, and other business partners and affiliates

Other requests you make (e.g. to send an event to a web-based calendar)

| 

  * To fulfill that specific request

**What information do we disclose?**

We Only _Share_ Your Personally Identifiable Information with _Outside Parties_ When:  
  
---  
  
  * You have provided your explicit consent to share the information.
  * We find that your actions on our Site violate our Terms of Use agreement to the extent that an outside investigation is warranted.
  * We believe doing so is necessary to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of TAP and its Users.
  * We sell or otherwise transfer such information to a successor or subsidiary of TAP.
  * We use a third-party subcontractor with its own secure privacy practices, e.g. for mailings and payment processing
  * It is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that TAP determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; or
  * It is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by TAP and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.

We will provide you with notice if we believe we are compelled to comply with a third party’s request for information.  
  
**User Accounts**

For those who opt in to register as member and/or sign up to receive E-news from TAP, TAP will regularly send you email newsletters.  For those who subscribe, TAP reserves the right to send promotional emails about products and services we and our marketing partners offer, and occasional news regarding TAP.

We provide Users the opportunity to opt out of receiving any further communications from us when they receive emails from us. We also give users the option of contacting us at any time to remove their information from our database or to stop future distributions to them of email updates or other information.

**Contact Us/Opting Out   **

TAP has appointed a privacy officer, who is accountable for compliance with these privacy principles and can answer any questions you may have.  You may contact the privacy officer by e-mail at privacy@tapinto.net.

You can opt out of any feature or reach us for any reason by sending an email to [contact@tapinto.net](mailto:contact@tapinto.net), or you can send mail to the following postal address:

**TAP IP LLC**  
P.O. Box 794  
New Providence, NJ 07974  
Attn: Website Coordinator

We also give you the option of changing or modifying any information you have previously provided to us. To do so, you should send an email to contact@tapinto.net, or contact the address above.

Despite our reasonable precautions to protect your information from loss, misuse or alteration, you should recognize that there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet. To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of any password you set up in registering for TAP’s service or making purchases on the Site.

**Accuracy and Security of Personal Information**

TAP uses encryption technology to safeguard your credit card data used in electronic transactions. Any personal information you provide to TAP is kept on secure servers. TAP uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures (a) to safeguard personal information against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification; and (b) to ensure the integrity of the personal information.

TAP disclaims any and all liability should the reasonable measures used by TAP to protect your private and personal information fail. TAP is not liable or responsible for any conduct by third parties, including conduct that results in theft and/or dissemination of your personal and/or private information.

**Use of Cookies**

To enhance your experience with TAP, our server uses "cookies" to store user's preferences. Cookies are messages sent between TAP and your browser which are saved as text files on your computer. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, requesting email alerts or additional information. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in cookies.

Users may customize their browsers to not accept cookies. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the Site, it is possible that some parts of the Site will not function properly, and you will not be able to experience personalized visits to the TAP Site or subscribe to any service offerings on the Site.

**Requesting Your Information and California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act.  In addition to the information we’ve provided above, on request we can provide more information about (i) the information we collect and how third parties use it, (ii) contact information and addresses of such third parties, and (iii) information about the products or Sites those third parties market.  Please send such requests to “TAP California User Choice Notice” at the address above.  Once you receive this information, you may request that we modify or remove any of your personal information.  We reserve the right to verify your identity before sending you this information. 

**“Do Not Track” Browser Signals**

We currently do not actively respond to Do Not Track browser signals and do not authorize the collection of personal information from Users through technologies deployed in advertising on the site. 

**Access to Children**

There are no features of this Site directed to children under the age of 13.  Those under 13 may not use any interactive features of this Site, order products, or post images on the Site. 

**Jurisdiction and Data Storage**

Please be aware that content submitted to TAP will be transferred to a data center in the United States.  If you post information to the Site, you are confirming your consent to such information being hosted and accessed in the United States.  Privacy laws or regulations in your country may differ from those in the United States, where TAP operates from, and whose laws govern this Privacy Policy.

**Policy Governs Use; Changes to Privacy Policy**  
The terms of this policy will govern the use and any information collected while it is in place. TAP reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting revisions on the Site. Changes to this privacy policy will be effective at the time they are posted to the Site. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not, create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

By using this Site, you agree to the terms as well as any posted changes of this Privacy Policy.  By using this Site, you hereby consent to the collection and use of this information by TAP.  If you do not agree to the terms, DO NOT use our Site.
